[left hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [right hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp a wooden block | [right hand] grasp a wooden block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the wooden block onto a growing stack | [right hand] place the wooden block onto the growing stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [right hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp a wooden block | [right hand] grasp a wooden block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the wooden block onto the growing stack | [right hand] place the wooden block onto the growing stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp a wooden block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the wooden block onto the growing stack | [ego] stay still
[left hand] reach toward scattered wooden blocks | [ego] stay still
[left hand] grasp a wooden block | [ego] stay still
[left hand] place the wooden block onto the growing stack | [ego] stay still